fabulously40.com 2008-05-02

# Fabulously40.com : The social network for women in their 40s and up

### Fabulously 40 Inc. Website Privacy Statement

### Privacy Policy

Fabulously40 presents resources for the purpose of informing, entertaining, and creating a community among Fabulously40 Visitors, and Registered Users; Fabulously40s intent is not to provide comprehensive information or advice on a particular topic. You should not rely on information provided by Fabulously40 to suggest a reliable course of action for an individual with legal, financial, educational, medical, or mental health concerns. The information contained here should not replace a consultation with a qualified expert in the field, such as an attorney, accountant, financial or investment advisor, teacher, physician, health care provider, or therapist outside of Fabulously40

### 1\. Acknowledgement and acceptance of terms

Fabulously40 Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing www.fabulously40.com website, you acknowledge and fully understand Fabulously40 Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

### 2\. Participating Merchant Policies

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in Fabulously40 services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

### 3\. Information We Collect and How We Use It

Fabulously40 Inc collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.

### Web Server Logs.

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:

Your Internet protocol address.

The kind of browser or computer you use.

Number of links you click within the site.

State or country from which you accessed the site.

Date and time of your visit.

Name of your Internet service provider.

Web page you linked to our site from.

Pages you viewed on the site.

### Use of Cookies

Fabulously40 Inc. may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.

Fabulously40 Inc reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into www.fabulously40.com a site that relies on third-party cookies).

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

### Personal Information Users

Fabulously40 is intended to be an Internet destination where individuals may exchange various viewpoints and ideas. The interactive nature of postings on Fabulously40 makes it impossible for us to assume responsibility for any of the materials posted by Registered Users. The opinions, recommendations, ideas, comments, and observations made by Fabulously40 users, and any photographs, data, text, video, music, sound, chat, messages, files or other material provided to us by Fabulously40 Registered Users (all of which are referred to as User Content) are not endorsed by Fabulouslsly40. At no time Fabulously40 guaranties reliability, accuracy, or quality of any User Content that is posted on the Web site. You recognize and accept that you will evaluate and bear any risks related to your use of any User Content, including any reliance on the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of such User Content. All User Content posted to the Web site is the sole responsibility of the person who originally posted the User Content, and your sole recourse for any damage you may suffer as a result of User Content shall be to such individual.

Event though Fabulously40 does not claim any ownership rights in User Content, by submitting User Content, you are representing that you are the creator of the material you submit, or have authorization to distribute it.

Once your content is posted on Fabulously40 you continue to retain your ownership rights in such User Content, and you continue to have the right to use your User Content in any way you choose. By sending User Content to Fabulously40, or posting it on the Web site, you expressly grant Fabuloulsy40 a worldwide, royalty-free, and non-exclusive license to publicly display, use, reproduce, modify, create derivative works from, and distribute the User Content in any form, in connection with the Fabulously40 Web site or other affiliated or related Fabuloulsy40 ventures. This license is sublicensable (so that Fabuloulsy40 is able to use its affiliates and subcontractors such as Internet content delivery networks to provide the Fabulously40 Web site and any other Fabulously40 services). 

If you choose to post User Content on Fabulously40 Web pages, we require that you adhere to generally accepted rules of etiquette and standards of behavior, and that your use of Fabulously40 reflects your respect for the legal rights of users connected with Fabulously40. In particular, you agree to the Rules of Conduct posted below (though this is not meant as an exhaustive list). You also agree that, if you post User Content containing adult or sexually explicit material, you will mark the User Content as such; 

we suggest that you preface your posting with the following legend: Warning: adult or sexually explicit material follows.

You acknowledge that Fabulously40 may or may not pre-screen User Content, but that Fabulously40 and its designees shall have the right (but not the obligation) in their sole discretion to pre-screen, refuse, move or remove any User Content from the Web site, with or without notice.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

To fulfill your service requests for services.

To protect ourselves from liability,

To respond to legal process or comply with law, or

In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

### 4\. Use of Web Beacons or GIF files

Fabulously40 Inc./www.fabulously40.com Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons sometimes also called single-pixel gifs that allow Fabulously40 Inc. to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Fabulously40 Inc. may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon

.

Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. Fabulously40 Inc prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

### 5\. Accessing Web Account Information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant info@fabulously40.com

### 8\. Changes to this Statement

Fabulously40 Inc has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the updated date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

### 7\. Copyright

All Fabulously40s content is protected under the copyright and intellectual property laws of the United States and other countries. Fabulously40 Web site also includes works that are the property of others, such as individual contributors or experts; these works, too, are protected by copyright and other intellectual property laws. Any redistribution, retransmission, or publication of any copyrighted material is strictly prohibited without the express written consent of the copyright owner. You agree not to change or delete any proprietary notices from materials downloaded from Fabulously40.

### 8\. Contacting Us

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us. Fabulously40 Inc or send your comments to : Fabulously 40 Inc. P.O. Box 902 Del Mar, California 92014

Fabulously40 Inc.  
Attention: Privacy Statement Personal  
P.O. Box 902 Del Mar Ca 92014

Fabulously40 Inc will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
